[
    {
        "question" :"Which team won IPL 2020 Title",
        "options":["SRH","CSK","MII","RCB"],
        "answer":"MII"
    
    },
    {
        "question" :"Which team won IPL 2018 Title",
        "options":["SRH","CSK","MII","RCB"],
        "answer":"CSK"
    
    },
    
    {
        "question" :"Which team won IPL 2017 Title",
        "options":["SRH","CSK","MII","RCB"],
        "answer":"MII"
    
    },
    
    {
        "question" :"Which team won IPL 2016 Title",
        "options":["SRH","CSK","MII","RCB"],
        "answer":"SRH"
    
    },
    
    {
        "question" :"Which team won IPL 2015 Title",
        "options":["SRH","CSK","MII","RCB"],
        "answer":"MII"
    
    },
    {
        "question" :"Which team won IPL 2014 Title",
        "options":["SRH","CSK","MII","KKR"],
        "answer":"KKR"
    
    },
    
    {
        "question" :"Which team won IPL 2013 Title",
        "options":["SRH","CSK","MII","RCB"],
        "answer":"MII"
    
    },
    {
        "question" :"Which team won IPL 2012 Title",
        "options":["SRH","KKR","MII","RCB"],
        "answer":"KKR"
    
    },
    
    {
        "question" :"Which team won IPL 2011 Title",
        "options":["SRH","CSK","MII","RCB"],
        "answer":"CSK"
    
    },
    {
        "question" :"Which team won IPL 2010 Title",
        "options":["SRH","CSK","MII","RCB"],
        "answer":"CSK"
    
    }
    
    
]
